Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 3: Boxes 46-66
Archives Information File, Section 3: Boxes 46-66
- Box: 60, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Employment Opportunities Involving Jobs Overseas, Foreign Languages, Travel, Publication (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Box: 60, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Occupation of Workers in Connecticut and the Northeast Region, 1967; Publication (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Box: 60, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Impact of Population Changes on State Programs, 1965; Publication (Box 60, Folder 8)
    Author: George O. Von Frank
    Notes: November 19, 1965
  - Item 2: Population Projection, Publication (Box 60, Folder 8)
    Author: J.C. Myles
  - Item 3: The Hudson Population, Publication (Box 60, Folder 8)
    Author: New York Office for Regional Development
  - Item 4: Population Changes Since 1960, 1965; Publication (Box 60, Folder 8)
    Author: New York Office for Local Government
    Notes: December 1965
- Box: 60, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Proposed Bill and Supporting Report on Employee-Management Relations in the Public Service, 1962; Publication (Box 60, Folder 9)
    Author: Anthony P. Savarese
- Box: 60, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: A Study of Collective Negotiation Impasses, 1969; Publication (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: An Act, 1969; Publication (Box 60, Folder 10)
    Author: New York Senate
    Notes: March 4, 1969
- Box: 60, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Step by Step with Mr. Raskin, Publication (Box 60, Folder 11)
    Author: Raskin
  - Item 2: The New York City Newspaper Strike: A Step-By-Step Account, 1963; Publication (Box 60, Folder 11)
    Author: A.H. Raskin
    Notes: April 1, 1963
- Box: 60, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The Harvests of Knowledge, 1957; Publication (Box 60, Folder 12)
    Author: Theodore C. Blegen
- Box: 60, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Burden of Blame, 1968; Publication (Box 60, Folder 13)
    Author: New York Civil Liberties Union
    Notes: October 9, 1968
- Box: 60, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Transit Strike Highlights, 1967; Publication (Box 60, Folder 14)
    Author: Tri-State Transportation Commission
  - Item 2: The Effect of the 1966 New York City Transit Strike on the Travel Behavior of Regular Transit Users, Publication (Box 60, Folder 14)
    Author: New York City Transit Authority
- Box: 60, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Newspaper Discrimination, 1942; Publication (Box 60, Folder 15)
    Author: Edgar Dale, Verna Spicer
    Notes: April 1942
- Box: 60, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Mining and Manufacturing Industries in Nicaragua, 1946; Publication (Box 60, Folder 16)
- Box: 60, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Night Work for Women, 1946; Publication (Box 60, Folder 17)
- Box: 60, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Report of the Committee on Night Baking, 1951; Publication (Box 60, Folder 18)
    Notes: October 1951
- Box: 60, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Women Who Work at Night, Publication (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Trends in Night Work for Women in New York State Factories, Publication (Box 60, Folder 19)
- Box: 60, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Night Work for Women, 1942; Publication (Box 60, Folder 20)
    Notes: June 1942
  - Item 2: State Laws Relating to Night Work for Women, 1948; Publication (Box 60, Folder 20)
    Notes: October 1, 1948
- Box: 60, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Occupational Deafness, Publication (Box 60, Folder 21)
    Author: Michael Wood
  - Item 2: Noise and Hearing, Publication (Box 60, Folder 21)
- Box: 60, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Employee Health & Welfare Benefits, 1974; Publication (Box 60, Folder 22)
    Notes: October 1974
- Box: 60, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: People -- Our Most Important Resource, Publication (Box 60, Folder 23)
    Author: North Carolina Agricultural Extension Service
- Box: 60, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Guide to Norweigan Statistics, 1963; Publication (Box 60, Folder 24)
    Author: Norway Central Bureau of Statistics
    Language: Norwegian; English.
  - Item 2: Guide to Norwegian Statistics, 1969; Publication (Box 60, Folder 24)
- Box: 60, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Residence and Migration of Students in Professional Nursing Programs, Publication (Box 60, Folder 25)
- Box: 60, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Selected Bibliography on Economic Security, 1967; Publication (Box 60, Folder 26)
    Author: American Nurses' Association
- Box: 60, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: The Industrial Nurse and the Woman Worker, 1949; Publication (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: Guiding Principles and Procedures for Industrial Nurses, Publication (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: Nursing Part Time in Industry, Publication (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Item 4: Occupational Health Nurses, 1966; Publication (Box 60, Folder 27)
- Box: 60, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Influence of Wage Rates on Nurse Mobility, Publication (Box 60, Folder 28)
    Author: Phil M. Smith
  - Item 2: Residential Care Enterprises, 1973; Publication (Box 60, Folder 28)
- Box: 60, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Nurse Supply and Needs, 1966; Publication (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - Item 2: Health Manpower Source Book, 1966; Publication (Box 60, Folder 29)
- Box: 60, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 60, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: In Pursuit of Quality, 1964; Publication (Box 60, Folder 30)
    Author: National League for Nursing
  - Item 2: Hospital Nursing Service Manual, 1950; Publication (Box 60, Folder 30)
    Author: American Hospital Association
  - Item 3: Professional Nursing Occupations, Publication (Box 60, Folder 30)
- Box: 60, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 60, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Conditions of Labour in the Cashewnut Processing Industry in India, 1954; Publication (Box 60, Folder 31)
    Author: India Labor Bureau
- Box: 60, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 60, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Outline of the New York State Industrial Nutrition Program, 1945; Publication (Box 60, Folder 32)
    Author: New York Emergency Food Commission
    Notes: October 15, 1945
- Box: 60, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 60, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Tuberculosis in Industry, 1949; Publication (Box 60, Folder 33)
    Author: Industrial Hygiene Foundation
  - Item 2: The Protection of Workers from Radiation Hazards, Publication (Box 60, Folder 33)
    Author: Association of Scientific Workers
  - Item 3: The Health of the Worker, Publication (Box 60, Folder 33)
    Author: Metropolitan Life Insurance Co.
  - Item 4: Recent Trends in Occupational Disease Legislation, Publication (Box 60, Folder 33)
  - Item 5: Methyl Bromide Poisoning, Publication (Box 60, Folder 33)
  - Item 6: Anthraco-Silicosis, 1943; Publication (Box 60, Folder 33)
  - Item 7: Emphysema in Industry, 1966; Publication (Box 60, Folder 33)
    Author: Industrial Hygiene Foundation of America
- Box: 60, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 60, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: A Clinical and Sanitary Study of the Fur and Hatters' Fur Trade, 1915; Publication (Box 60, Folder 34)
    Author: Louis I. Harris
    Notes: December 1915
- Box: 60, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 60, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Notes on the Diagnosis of Occupational Diseases, 1950; Publication (Box 60, Folder 35)
    Author: Great Britain Ministry of National Insurance
- Box: 60, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 60, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Selected Health Characteristics by Occupation, 1963; Publication (Box 60, Folder 36)
- Box: 60, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 60, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Geographic and Occupational Mobility of Rural Manpower, Publication (Box 60, Folder 37)
    Author: Organisation for Economic Co- Operation and Development
  - Item 2: Occupational Mobility, 1964; Publication (Box 60, Folder 37)
  - Item 3: Mobility of Disadvantaged Groups, Publication (Box 60, Folder 37)
    Author: Patricia Bowen
  - Item 4: Labor Mobility, 1967; Publication (Box 60, Folder 37)
    Notes: April 1967
  - Item 5: The Job Ladder as a Device for Developing Human Resources, Publication (Box 60, Folder 37)
    Author: U.S. Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research
- Box: 60, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 60, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Rehabilitation in the Soft-Coal Fields, Publication (Box 60, Folder 38)
    Author: American Friends Service Committee
- Box: 60, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 60, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: New Careers, Publication (Box 60, Folder 39)
    Author: Frank Riessman
  - Item 2: Characteristics of Michigan's Labor Force, 1965; Publication (Box 60, Folder 39)
    Notes: December 14, 1965
  - Item 3: Looking Ahead to a Career, Publication (Box 60, Folder 39)
  - Item 4: Evaluation of Results and Administration of the Job Opportunities in the Business Sector Program in Five Cities, 1971; Publication (Box 60, Folder 39)
    Notes: March 24, 1971
  - Item 5: Current Occupation and Past Training of Adult Workers, 1968; Publication (Box 60, Folder 39)
    Author: Office of Statistical Standards
  - Item 6: Prospective Occupations, Publication (Box 60, Folder 39)
    Author: Bureau of Employment Security
  - Item 7: Suggestions for Making and Reporting Occupational Surveys, 1939; Publication (Box 60, Folder 39)
    Author: Lester K. Ade
- Box: 61, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Occupational Trends in New York City, 1933; Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
    Author: National Occupational Conference
    Notes: April 1933
- Box: 61, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Rhode Island Skill Survey, 1967; Publication (Box 61, Folder 2)
    Author: Rhode Island Department of Employment Security
- Box: 61, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Population Census, 1960; Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
    Author: South Africa Bureau of Census and Statistics
    Language: Dutch; English.
- Box: 61, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: An Analysis of Community Occupational Surveys, 1949; Publication (Box 61, Folder 4)
    Author: The Stout Institute
- Box: 61, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The 1965 Third Edition of the Dictionary of Occupational Titles, 1968; Publication (Box 61, Folder 5)
    Author: Sidney A. Fine
    Notes: December 1968
- Box: 61, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Wisconsin Manpower Outlook, Publication (Box 61, Folder 6)
    Author: Wisconsin Employment Service
- Box: 61, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Unionization of White Collar Workers, 1947; Publication (Box 61, Folder 7)
    Author: Robert K. Burns
    Notes: February 22, 1947
- Box: 61, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Automation and Employment Opportunities for Officeworkers, Publication (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Education for Office Employment, Publication (Box 61, Folder 8)
    Author: National Office Management Association
  - Item 3: Clerical Occupations for Women, Publication (Box 61, Folder 8)
- Box: 61, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Work Injuries to Office Employees, Publication (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Box: 61, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Mittelpunkt, Publication (Box 61, Folder 10)
    Author: Pressestelle der Bundesversicherungsanstalt fur Angestellte
- Box: 61, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Wages and Hours in Law Offices and in Real Estate, 1960; Publication (Box 61, Folder 11)
- Box: 61, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Community Salary Survey, 1969; Publication (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Industry Wage Survey, 1961; Publication (Box 61, Folder 12)
    Notes: May-July 1961
  - Item 3: Salary Table No.47, 1967; Publication (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Community Salary Survey, 1968; Publication (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Community Salary Survey, 1971; Publication (Box 61, Folder 12)
- Box: 61, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Which Way Is Up?, 1965; Publication (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Selecting Office Workers, 1952; Publication (Box 61, Folder 13)
    Author: Robert L. Peterson
- Box: 61, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Keep Cool and Calm About Office Collections, Publication (Box 61, Folder 14)
    Author: Ben Ashell
  - Item 2: Cutting Office Costs, Publication (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: The Flexible Work Force, Publication (Box 61, Folder 14)
    Author: Elmer L. Winter
  - Item 4: Production Planning and Control in Office Operations, 1949; Publication (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Office Personnel Practices, 1968; Publication (Box 61, Folder 14)
    Author: Federated Employers of the Bay Area
    Notes: Midyear 1968
  - Item 6: Office Personnel Practices, 1964; Publication (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Box: 61, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Bibliography for Administrative Management, 1963; Publication (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Box: 61, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Clerical Cost Control, Publication (Box 61, Folder 16)
    Author: Carl Aspinall
  - Item 2: Spiraling Office Costs, 1965; Publication (Box 61, Folder 16)
    Author: Harold M. Sholder
- Box: 61, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Administering the Forms Program, Publication (Box 61, Folder 17)
- Box: 61, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Appraisal and Control of Duplicating Service, 1949; Publication (Box 61, Folder 18)
- Box: 61, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Human Relations Fundamentals for Retail Credit Employees, Publication (Box 61, Folder 19)
    Author: National Retail Credit Association
  - Item 2: Modernizing Office Procedures, Publication (Box 61, Folder 19)
- Box: 61, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Automation Impact on Training of Present and Future Office Employees, Publication (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Office Automation and the Non-Manual Worker, Publication (Box 61, Folder 20)
- Box: 61, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The Older Population of New York State, 1957; Publication (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Our Nation's Senior Citizens, 1963; Publication (Box 61, Folder 21)
    Author: U.S. Special Committee on Aging
  - Item 3: Action for the Aged and Aging, 1961; Publication (Box 61, Folder 21)
- Box: 61, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Observation on Care of the Aging in Europe, 1961; Publication (Box 61, Folder 22)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Veterans' Affairs
    Notes: September 11, 1961
  - Item 2: A New Day for the Older American, Publication (Box 61, Folder 22)
    Author: President's Council on Aging
  - Item 3: Old Age -- An American Problem, 1949; Publication (Box 61, Folder 22)
    Author: Robert J. Havighurst
  - Item 4: The Added Years, 1960; Publication (Box 61, Folder 22)
    Author: New York Committee of One Hundred
    Notes: November 1, 1960
  - Item 5: Prominent Senior Citizens on Film, 1965; Publication (Box 61, Folder 22)
    Author: Jack B. Spear
- Box: 61, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: The Care of Old People, Publication (Box 61, Folder 23)
    Author: Kenneth Thompson, John Vaughan-Morgan, Angus Maude
  - Item 2: Centers for Older People, 1962; Publication (Box 61, Folder 23)
    Author: National Council on Aging
    Notes: October 26-28, 1962
  - Item 3: Developments in Aging, 1966; Publication (Box 61, Folder 23)
    Notes: March 15, 1966
  - Item 4: Characteristics of the Population Covered Under the Guaranteed Income Supplement of the Old Age Security Program, 1967; Publication (Box 61, Folder 23)
    Author: Ottawa Department of Health and Welfare
  - Item 5: Digest of Study Report on Old Age Project, Publication (Box 61, Folder 23)
    Author: Wilma Winnick
- Box: 61, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Education for a Long and Useful Life, 1950; Publication (Box 61, Folder 24)
    Author: U.S. Office of Education
  - Item 2: Family Relationships of Older People, Publication (Box 61, Folder 24)
- Box: 61, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Georgia's Story of Her Aging, 1961; Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
    Author: Governors Commission on Aging
  - Item 2: Hawaii and its Senior Citizens, 1965; Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
    Author: Hawaii Commission on Aging
  - Item 3: Major Federal Legislative and Executive Actions Affecting Senior Citizens, 1965; Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
    Author: U.S. Special Commission on Aging
  - Item 4: Major Federal Legislative and Executive Actions Affecting Senior Citizens, 1964; Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Item 5: New Population Facts on Older Americans, 1961; Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
    Notes: May 24, 1961
  - Item 6: Has Old Age a Place in a Young Man's World?, 1949; Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
    Author: Newsweek
    Notes: September 1949
- Box: 61, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: On Growing Older, 1964; Publication (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: Older Americans Act Amendments of 1969, Publication (Box 61, Folder 26)
    Notes: August 5, 1969
- Box: 61, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Report to the President, Publication (Box 61, Folder 27)
- Box: 61, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Senior Citizens in Kalamazoo, 1961; Publication (Box 61, Folder 28)
    Author: William D. Allen, Samuel V. Bennett
    Notes: May 1961
  - Item 2: White House Conference on Aging, 1961; Publication (Box 61, Folder 28)
    Notes: January 9-12, 1961
  - Item 3: Services for Senior Citizens, 1964; Publication (Box 61, Folder 28)
    Notes: September 11, 1964
- Box: 61, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Aging: Progressive Programming, Publication (Box 61, Folder 29)
    Author: American Public Welfare Association
- Box: 61, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 61, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Old Age Dependency, Publication (Box 61, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: Care of the Aged in Norway, Publication (Box 61, Folder 30)
    Author: Grondahl & Sons Boktrykkeri
  - Item 3: General Information on Old Age Assistance, 1946; Publication (Box 61, Folder 30)
    Author: New York Department of Social Welfare
    Notes: September 1946
- Box: 61, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 61, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Old Age Dependency, 1928; Publication (Box 61, Folder 31)
    Author: California Department of Social Welfare
- Box: 61, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: State Services for Connecticut's Older Persons, Publication (Box 61, Folder 32)
    Author: Connecticut Commission on Services for Elderly Persons
- Box: 61, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 61, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: A Study of Old Age Assistance Recipients in New Mexico, 1965; Publication (Box 61, Folder 33)
    Author: New Mexico Department of Public Welfare
- Box: 61, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 61, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Report of the Pennsylvania Commission on Old Age Assistance, 1925; Publication (Box 61, Folder 34)
    Author: Pennsylvania Commission on Old Age Assistance
    Notes: January 1925
- Box: 61, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 61, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Pensionarernas Riksorganisation och Partipolitiken, 1966; Publication (Box 61, Folder 35)
    Author: Rolf Och Lena Norberg
- Box: 61, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Old Age Assistance, 1943; Publication (Box 61, Folder 36)
    Author: Peter Kasius
  - Item 2: Services to the Elderly on Public Assistance, 1966; Publication (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - Item 3: Major Federal Legislative and Executive Actions Affecting Senior Citizens, 1964; Publication (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - Item 4: Federal Payments to Older Persons in Need of Protection, 1965; Publication (Box 61, Folder 36)
    Author: U.S. President's Council on Aging
    Notes: Spring 1965
- Box: 61, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 61, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Services to the Elderly on Public Assistance, 1965; Publication (Box 61, Folder 37)
    Notes: August 18-19, 1965
- Box: 61, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 61, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Health Care for the Aged in the State of Washington, Publication (Box 61, Folder 38)
    Author: Odin W. Anderson, William T. Reich
- Box: 61, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 61, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Laws Relating to Old-Age Assistance, 1962; Publication (Box 61, Folder 39)
    Author: Wisconsin Department of Public Welfare
- Box: 61, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 61, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Classified Bibliography on Geriatrics and the Care of the Aged, 1948; Publication (Box 61, Folder 40)
    Author: John J. Griffin
  - Item 2: The Noncash Needs of Aged Persons Affecting Their Individual and Social Security, 1948; Publication (Box 61, Folder 40)
    Author: Florence A. Armstrong
    Notes: March 1948
  - Item 3: A Selective Bibliography on the Welfare of Older People, 1949; Publication (Box 61, Folder 40)
    Author: New York City Welfare Council
  - Item 4: Aging, Religion, and the Church, Publication (Box 61, Folder 40)
    Author: The National Council on the Aging
- Box: 62, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Action for the Aging, Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Author: University of North Dakota
  - Item 2: Research in Gerontology, Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Author: White House Conference on Aging
  - Item 3: Seminar on Community Planning for Older Adults, 1961; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Author: Brandeis University
    Notes: August 27 - September 1, 1961
  - Item 4: Creating Opportunities for Older Persons, Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Box: 62, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: A Survey of State and Community Programs for the Aging, 1965; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Author: New York Office for the Aging
- Box: 62, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Directory of Services for the Aging in New York State, 1962; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
    Notes: February 1962
- Box: 62, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Plejehjem Idag Og I Fremtiden, 1965; Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
    Author: Hjorring amt
- Box: 62, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: A Lifetime of Living, 1962; Publication (Box 62, Folder 5)
    Author: H. Mason Atwood
- Box: 62, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Rights and Responsibilities, 1965; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Social Security for the Aged: International Perspectives, 1969; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
    Notes: August 1969
- Box: 62, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Act, 1967; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Author: Republic of South Africa
    Language: English; Dutch.
  - Item 2: Elevacion de las Pensiones de Jubilacion, Viudedad y Orfandad, 1971; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Author: Instituto Ecuatoriano de Seguridad Social
  - Item 3: Fortidspensionen Reformeras, 1970; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Author: Sven F. Bengston
  - Item 4: Samfundet Og de Aeldre, 1969; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Author: Socialministeriet
  - Item 5: Welfare of the Aged in Denmark, 1963; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Author: Kirtsen Rudfeld
  - Item 6: Richtig Rentenversichern!, 1966; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Author: Alfons Kulinski
    Notes: July 25, 1966
  - Item 7: 1966 Ars Pensionsuppgorelser SAF-SIF, SAF-SALF, SAF-HTF, Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)